So I found this plug-in called stage
wise that allow you to do very granular
UI updates and changes with cursor by
communicating and selecting specific UI
elements that you want to make changes
because quite often when you use cursor
to implement UI applications it will get
you to 80% of what you want but they're
just like last 10 to 20% of UI that
didn't looks right and you want to make
changes and those kind of granular
changes often not that easy. What stage
wise does is that it allow you to select
very specific UI elements directly in
browser and communicate those elements
to cursor very effectively. Here is how
you can set up. So we can go to cursor
extension search for stage wise and you
should be able to just install the
extension here directly. Once installed,
you can open cursor in any existing web
project and all you need to do just do
command shiftp and search for stage wise
and it will have this auto setup stage
wise toolbar
option. If you click on that it should
trigger a message in the chat on the
right side where it will start setting
up stage wise properly in your existing
project. So it will automatically look
at package to understand did you build
the whole web app in Nex.js or react and
use the right package and setup and once
it's done you can accept and now if you
run this web project at the bottom you
will see this floating bar and you can
just click on that and then you'll be
able to choose any UI elements on the
screen. So I can select this button or I
can select multiple button as well if I
want and give a prompt make all buttons
border radio larger let's say and if I
send it on the right side you can see it
will automatically trigger a message in
cursor inside this message it has
special prompt it will include specific
prompt that you just put in the URL as
well as detailed information of the UI
elements that you selected so if I
accept it and now you can see all the
buttons are fully rounded
And cool part of using stage wise is
because it is communicate very clearly
specific div element as well as relevant
class. Then when make change it will
actually make global change across all
the similar
elements instead of just changing one
specific elements. And if you want you
can also select multiple which is really
useful. You can also do a bit more like
sophisticated change that will be a bit
difficult to communicate. For
example, I can choose this show more
button as well as space here where it is
used to show the labels and give it
prompt. I want to making sure text and
show more button are in line on same row
where text on the left and show more
button on the right. And now you can see
that it is on the same row but I want it
to be like right align. So I can choose
this thing again and give a prompt.
This weights should be
100%. So show more button is like right
side floating. So now you can see that
show more button is on the right side
and the the tag is on the left. So this
example of how can you use stage wise to
do this. UI fine-tuning very easily.
There are more cool examples on their
website where you can like do a bit more
sophisticated change on the UI by
selecting those items and convert them
into like accordion or change a table's
label into a different color very easily
and accurately. And what I saw really
cool is how they implement this
interaction that directly send message
inside the cursor. This kind of achieves
some really interesting UX that I didn't
think of before. And I'm sure this is
just like starting point of stage wise
plugin. There probably more
functionalities I imagine they were
adding. So this is just one example of
how can you use uh tools like stage wise
to fine-tune the UI further. If you're
interested, you can join AI builder club
where I share advanced tips and tricks
about AI codings and building production
ready large model application from
either myself and other industry
experts. And we also provide tools like
SAS launch kit as well as tax coder that
will help you generate prd and cursor
rules. So if you're interested feel free
to join EI builder club. Thank you and I
see you next